I'm running seven marathons on all seven
continents in one week starting in
Africa.
This is called the Great World Race and
it's a challenge I'm honestly not sure
if I'll be able to finish, but I'm
really excited to try. My goal is to try
and finish each marathon this week in
around 5 hours.
>> One mile done, 182.4
to go. But I quickly realized that it's
totally different from a big city
marathon where there are thousands of
people running with you and you can fall
in line with a group to stay on target.
I struggled to find anyone who was
around my pace for an extended period of
time, so it was a bit lonely. But there
were a few moments I got to have
conversations with other racers which
really lifted my spirits. Like Nick
here.
>> This is Nick's first ever marathon.
>> [music]
>> And he's doing seven this week. Or Tweek
who is running in a suit to raise
awareness for men's mental health.
>> Mile 21.
>> Yeah.
Five to go.
Luckily I finished the race right on
target thanks to the much needed energy
of the Challenge Accepted community who
came out to support. Thank you all so
much.
>> it. You're the sweetest. But there was
very little time to celebrate. We just
finished the Cape Town Marathon a few
hours ago and we are now boarding an
airplane to Antarctica where we're going
to race at midnight.
>> Which means I have to run two marathons
in 24 hours. Follow to see how that
goes.